怎么缩水啦?
Why, it's shrinking?
我早就跟你说过
I told you before not to have
叫你不要到这里来做西装嘛
Your suit made there
你看你看
Just look at it...
怎么会呀?
How come?
我妹妹昏倒了 ，怎么办…
My sister is black out, what shall I do?
你们帮帮她呀
You must help her
拜託你们快点来救救他呀
Please help her wake up
我妹妹昏倒了
My sister is fainted
你们帮忙来救救她呀
please help...
妹妹…
Sister...
真大，两只手都拿不过来
So big? I can't hold with both my hand
稀有动物呀
So rare
怎么办呀?
What shall we do?
就是啊，现在怎么办?
Yeah, what shall we do?
我怎么知道?硒士这么大
How can I know? She gets such big size
快点帮她做人工呼吸吧
Give her artificial respiration
我怎么没想到呢?
I didn't think of that
等一等
Wait
我妹妹从小到大，没有让男人碰过
My sister has never let a man touch her
我爸爸吩咐过
Dad said
如果那个男人要碰过
If any man touched her
那个男人就…
that man would...
就…就你妈个头呀，你快把她急救
Would you ass, Give her first aid quick
再不帮她人工呼吸，她就死定了
We don't give her artificial respiration she'll die
你完全说对了 ，再不帮她急救
You're so right
她就死定了
She'll die if we don't help her
我学过人工呼吸，我来帮她
I've learnt artificial respiration, I'll help her
找死啊你，要你多管闲事
Shit, it's out of your business
救人一命胜过七颗葡萄嘛
But it's important to rescue others
我不能见死不救，走开
I can't just let her die... get away
你有毛病呀?吸这么久呀
You are nut? Why it takes so long?
假牙都让你吸出来了
You suck the dentifrice out too
大哥呀，因为她胸特别大
Hey, as the super big breasts
所以，需要的氧气自然就多啦
So she needs more oxygen
我已经是供不应求了 ，你躲开点
Get aside as I'm working very hard now
帮我按住她肚子   好
Hold on her belly for me OK
笨手笨脚的，我来
You're so clumsy, let me do it
你行不行呀   我受不了
Can you manage? I can't manage
你会不会啊，快一点嘛
Do you know it? Be quick
你不要吃人家豆腐呀
Don't try to get benefit from her
他也不行了
He faints too
你没有本事就别死撑了 ，烦不烦
Don't pretend you can if you can't
怎么办?   对呀，怎么办…?
What to do? Yeah, how do?
帮个忙
Give me a hand
你少来，他会急救都昏了
Shit, he knows First Aid yet he fainted
我不会急救不就死了吗
I'll die as I don't know First Aid
那怎么办啦?怎么办啊?
What must we do?
什么怎么办?
What?
这个方法行不通就换个其它的方法
If this doesn't work, we'll try another way
先把她抱起来
Held her up first
你搬过来
Take her here
这也行呀，小心呀你
How can you do this? Be careful
用力呀，你长得跟牛一样
Harder, why are you weak when
怎么没力气啊
You're as strong as a bull
用力呀，帮她把水榨出来
Harder, let's maker her vomit out water
这样榨行不行呀?
Will this work?
废话，谁说不行呀   真行呀
Shit, of course it will It is really works
行啦，行啦，好像有效啊
It works... it works well
她好像醒了   放下来…
She's coming to now Put her down...
妹妹…
Sister...
行了吧，还说不行
You said it won't work? It proves right now
我知道行啦，可是喷得我满脸都是
I know it does, but I've it on all my face
臭死了   你呀，毛病最多了
It's stink too You, you are disgusting
给我一点水洗洗脸
Give me water to wash my face
先给她喝口水
Give her some to drink first
把她扶起来
Help her up
现在我们人也救完了,我们干什么?
What shall we do next now she's rescued?
我们流落荒岛
We're on desert island
船也沉了 ，问问领队
And our ship's sunk, let's ask guide
领队怎么办?   这怎么办呀?
Guide, what shall we do now?
各位团友，请大家稍安勿躁
Everybody, you mustn't get nervous
这个这个观光船虽然沉了
Though our ship is sunk
可是你们要相信我
But you must believe me
信，信你有屁用 ，你又不是信用卡
Believe? What's the use? You're not a credit card
你那个一表八千里的大表叔呢?
Where's your so-called uncle?
那边有个村子呀
There's a village over there
大表叔
Uncle
小心呀
Be careful
起来
Get up
你没事吧   没事
Are you alright? OK
我发现那边有个村子呀
I found a village there
那我们赶快去罢，远不远?
Let's hurry up there, is it far away?
不太远啊，就在山后面
Not far, it's just over the mountain
那就快点去啊，动作快点
Then let's go quick, move faster
那你们快点收拾东西，我先走啦
Pack your things and I'll go there first
小心点呀
Be careful
快，快点
Faster, be faster...
小心点
Be careful
慢慢走呀
Walk slowly
快呀，就快到了 ，走
Be quick, we'll soon arrive, come on
快…快
Faster...
我在这里休息一下
Let's take a rest here
累不累呀?   不累
Are you tired? No
你怎么搞的，到那儿都靠着我
Why must you stick to me wherever I go?
简直白痴
You're idiot
搞什么鬼呀你，白痴呀你
What are you doing? You idiot
撞人家痛死了
You hurt me
这是什么东西呀?你就拿来吃?
What is this? How can you just eat anything?
你也不怕吃死你呀
This may be poisonous
怕什么?我从小吃到大
Don't worry, I've always eaten them
很好呀呀，你尝尝
Just try some
我才不吃呢，要吃你自己吃
Never, Just eat them if you want
不过我可先声明呀，随便你怎么死
But I just tell you, no matter how you die
最要紧的是先还给我
You must first pay me back
欠我的三万零六百三十二块四
The $30,632.40 you owe me
还还还?
Pay back...
你不吃我吃
I'll eat if you won't
你们在干什么?
What are you doing?
这么走天黑都到不了那个村子
We won't get to the village if you walk like this
我可不等你们了
I won't wait for you
走, 快走
Walk faster, come on
你怎么老是跟你老公顶嘴呢?
Why do you keep quarrelling? You are married couple
夫妻俩呀，吵什么吵呢?
Why keep quarrelling?
这个夫妻床头打架床尾和
Will you stop the quarrel
少说一句算了
As you are married
妈的死胖子，你不要烦我老婆
Shit, Fatty, stop disturbing my wife
老个屁婆呀，我们又没有注册
What wife? We haven't been registered
老婆前老婆后的
Don't call me wife
原来你们两个没有结婚呀?
So you're not yet married?
没结婚就不是你老婆
Then she is not your wife
不是你老婆谁都可以追啦
Which means I can woo her now
你再胡说八道我对你不客气了
I'll teach you a lesson if you go on bullshit
什么?什么?怎样?怎么样呀…?
What? What do you want?
混蛋，你够了 ，你再胡说八道
Bastard, this is too much, if you bullshit again
我高兴说，我喜欢说
I like to say, I want say
我愿说，我就说
I will say, I'm going to say
还说?
Dare you say?
我还说，我说，我不吃了…
I say again, I say, I don't eat...
我掐死你…
I must strangle you
你们别打了
Don't fight
快点，快点，快…
Faster... be quick
快点，那边有房子呀   哪儿
Be quick, there's a house there Where?
我们去看看   走
Let's go and see Let's go
走快点呀   急死啦
Walk faster I have natural call
要嘘嘘呀?   是呀
You want toilet? Yes
来…
Come on...
去看看
Go and see
我看清楚没人了 ，快点嘘吧
I've checked, no one is here, be quick
对了 ，说对不起让让，知不知道
Right, say： excuse me, OK
我说过了
I've said it already
有的吃了
There's food
我给你吓死了   你这是干什么
You surprised me What are you doing?
你看，那么多吃的
Look, there's much food
你还不快蹲下来
Why don't you crouch down?
蹲下
Crouch?
是呀，快点啦
Yeah, be quick
老婆，你好重呀，你该减肥了
Wife, you are very heavy, you better go on a diet
快点啦
Be quick
小心点呀
Be careful
不要动啦，等一下再捡
Don't move, let's pick them up later
快点啦
Be quick
完了 ，老婆
Finish, wife
老婆，你怎么样啦?
How are you?
还问?把人家摔下来
Dare you ask? You made me fall down
还不快把裙子拿给我
Give me the dress quick
被人家看到怎么办?
It's bad to be spotted by others
你真没用啦，这么一点小事都弄砸
You're lousy, you just can't do even a minor thing
干什么?
What are you doing?
你不要过来呀
Don't come over
被我看到了
But I saw it
不许你看呀   挡也没用了呀
You mustn't peep It's no use covering
挡住我
Cover me
你全都让我看到   全给他看见了
I can see all He saw all
别挡住…    你别过来
Don't cover Don't come over
干什么，有什么好看呀
What are you doing? Nothing to see
你别过来
Don't come over
我全都看到了 ，来了…
I've seen everything, come on...
你不要乱来，再来我就翻脸啦
Don't act rashly, I'll beat you if you come near
翻脸，太棒了
Will you? It's great
抢到了 ，抢到了
Get it, get it
看什么，快把裙子拿给我嘛
Get me the dress quick
别急呀，他吃完就走
Don't worry, he will go away when he finishes eating
蛇呀
Snake
快点打死它啦，快点啦
Kill it quick...
快点，好吓人呀   打死它…
It's horrible Kill it
快点打死它，快
Kill it quick...
看什么呀你?
What are you looking at?
跑哪儿去了?不见啦?
Where is it? It's gone?
老公呀   老婆怎么啦?
Husband Wife, what is it?
蛇呀蛇呀   在哪里呀?
Snake... Where is it?
在后面…
Behind you...
后面?哪儿?
Behind? Where?
大蛇咬屁股…
The snake bites the bottoms...
过瘾…   打死它
Great... Kill it
让我来，你别怕
Let me kill it, don't be frighten
岂有此理，咬我老婆，我打死你…
Shit, dare you bite my wife? I must kill you
快点把它赶走呀，快点…
Cast it way quick...
没事啦，老婆，别怕
It's right, don't panic
蛇呀，蛇跑我裤子里去了
Snake, the snake gets into my trousers
活该
Wonderful
我小弟弟
My dick
不出来?我把你掏出来
Won't come out? I must take you out
抓到了
Got it
你不要过来
Don't come over
不要怕，你别过来
Don't scare, you don't come over
快来帮忙呀…
Come and help
你不要过来
Don't come over
你千万别过来
You mustn't come
快帮我把它抓住呀
Help me to catch it
救命呀…
Help
蛇被你抓死了   救命呀
You caught hold of snake Help
来，我来帮你   好
Coming, I'll help you Great
还有一道门呀
Another door
到底有多少门呀?
How many are there exactly?
你没事吧?
Are you OK?
看我的
Watch
你们怎么不管我了
I won't care about you
把她扶进来   好
Help her in
真是的
Shit
来，小心点呀
Coming, be careful
等一等
Hold it
这里有一盏灯，看能不能点着
There's a lamp here, see if you can light it?
别逗了你
Stupid
我看这灯的年纪比我们三个人的
It can't be lit as it looks older than
年纪加起都大点不着的
The three of us
也试试嘛，也许点得着呢
We might as well try, maybe it can be lit
你点点试试看，也许点得着呢
Try it, Maybe can light it
八千里表叔你没事吧?
Uncle, are you OK?
没事
I'm alright
火
Fire
没烧到你呀?
Did it burn you?
没有
No
我曾经听人家说日本人
I've heard people saying Japanese
跟中国人一样的迷信
Are as superstitious as Chinese
日本人有一种习惯
Japanese have a habit
只要在屋里挂起串纸鹤
Of protecting their house by hanging
就可以保平安了
Some paper crane
可是如果不小心，纸鹤烧起来的话
But if the paper cranes are burnt up
他们就非常害怕
They will be very afraid
认为是一个不祥的预兆
As they think this is an ominous sign
八千里表叔，你干什么呀?
Uncle, what are you trying to do?
把刀放开，你干什么
Put down the knife, what are you doing?
你想干什么? 你疯了你…
What do you want? Are you crazy?
把刀放开   不要再打了
Put down the knife Don't fight
这刀很锋利，你干什么呀?你疯了…
This knife is sharp, what are you doing? You crazy?
你为什么? 别打了 ，不要再打了
What happen? Don't fight...
喂，够了 ，不要再打了
Hey, that's enough, don't fight
八千里表叔，你怎么啦?
Uncle, what happens to you?
放手呀，把刀放下
Put down the knife
放手呀
Put down
别打了 ，你们不要再打了
Don't fight... don't fight any more
你还记不记得
Do you remember?
你妈怎么打你的?
How your mother used to beat you?
打他，脱鞋打他呀
Beat him, beat him with shoes
你放开手
Let go
我怎么了?
What happened to me?
你没受伤吧?   很痛呀
Do you get hurt? It's hurt
发生什么事啦?
What's going on?
对不起啊，大哥你千万不要见怪
Sorry, big brother, please don't blame on me
小孩子不懂事，冒犯你的
He's only a kid
请你原谅
Please excuse him
起来   这位大哥，对不起…
Get up Big brother, sorry...
我们快点走吧，这里很邪呀
Let's leave this place, it's mysterious
走吧
Let's go
你到那边看看
Look at that side
钻…钻石呀
Dia... Diamond
这么大的钻石
So bit a diamond
我的妈
Jesus
是真的呀
It's genuine
不知道几卡拉?
Don't know how many carats it is?
你干什么呀?
What do you want?
你找什么呀?走啦
What are you looking for? Let's go
好呀
Sure
你看见什么啦?
What did you see?
没有呀，我什么都没看到
Nothing, I saw nothing
对了 ，你呢?
Right, and you?
你有没有看到什么值钱的东西
Did you see anything precious?
像什么金银珠宝之类的?
Like gold, or jewels?
没有，这里的东西全都怪里怪气的
No, everything here looks strange
对对对，那走吧
Right, Let's go then
不见了
It's gone
钻石呀
Diamond
这钻石是我先找到的
I found this diamond first
杀死你，我要杀死你…
I must kill you...
杀死你呀，快死
幸亏没丢了
It's good it's not lost
你打我
You beat me?
就为了这个，你们两个打架呀?
You two fight just for this?
你怎么把它丢了?钻石呀
Why did you lose it? It's diamond
那种东西是用来镇邪的
This is for damping the evils
还是不要的好，快走
Don't take it, go away
三八?   你还四九呢
Bitch? You are
你们不觉得在这里混身不自在吗?
Don't you feel uneasy in here?
快走，走呀
Let's go, hurry up
真是? 快走呀
Really? Run faster
我肚子好痛呀
I suffer from belly
你们两个先走啦，我大便
You go first, I must go to toilet
你们快点啦，就在下面了
Be quick, it's down there
这里好恐怖呀
It's horrible here
总得找个地方过夜吧
We must find a place to sleep tonight
随便啦，也没得选择   走啦
We have no choice Let's go
走…   好…
Let's go... OK
凡是孤魂野鬼
All evils
都喜欢在这里环境出现
They will appear in this environment
尤其是渺无人烟的深谷幽谷和空屋
Especially in place without human
你学他睡得跟猪一样就不会怕啦
Sleep as a pig like him and you won't be afraid
你什么呀?他怎么睡着嘛
You what? Why can he sleep?
俗话说人怕鬼三分，鬼怕人七分
It's saying, human is afraid ghost but ghost is more afraid human
其实是无稽之谈
It's ridiculous
因为道行高深的野鬼根本不会怕人
As mighty ghosts don't fear human being
不要再讲了 ，我好害怕呀
Don't say any more, I'm scared
大哥呀，你吓死人啦
Brother, you scare me
不要说了行不行?
Can you keep quiet?
这什么故事嘛?那么恐怖噢
What story is this? It's frightening
好可怕呀，你搂着我好不好?
I'm scared, will you hold me?
你少来呀，搂着你像搂着个马桶
No, holding you, like holding a toilet bow
这种事别找我   你好讨厌啊
Don't ask me for that You're annoying
你知不知道你很臭啊?
Do you know you are stink?
比我的胳肢窝还臭
You are stinker than my armpit
人家都不嫌你臭
I didn't say you're stink so
你也不要嫌人家臭嘛
You mustn't say I'm stink either
你老是爱吃什么臭豆腐
You, you like eating stink tofu
臭鸭蛋，臭鸡蛋
Stink eggs
跟你在一块非染上狐臭不可，睡了
I'll become stink if I stick to you Let's sleep
那不是真的好，骂我臭?
Then we're two of a kind
你想干嘛呀?
What do you want?
关灯了   睡觉
Turn off the lights Sleep
关灯，关灯，不要吵了 ，大家睡觉
Turn off the lights... don't shout and go to sleep
你好臭呀，走开啦
You're stink, go away
难道我真的臭，我可不能这么臭的
Am I really stink? I can't be
在这样的环境洗澡很危险呀
But it's dangerous to take a bath here
叫我怎么洗呢，没有别的办法了
How can I take a bath? There's no other way
为了表示我的真情
To show my love
这个险非冒不可呀
I must take this risk
对不起让让啊
Sorry, excuse me
原来是你呀   你怎么偷看我呀
It's you? Why are you peeping me?
谁有那功夫偷看你洗澡呀
Who is peeping you?
你有什么宝呀
What good are you?
你跟我走呀，到我洗了 ，真是的
Go away, it's my turn to wash, shit
我警告你不许偷看我洗澡
I warn you not to peep me bathing
有洗澡地方不告诉我
You are so selfish as to wash
自己偷偷洗， 自私自利
Yourself and not tell me
不怎么臭嘛?
I don't smell, do I?
小鸟鸟，好多小鸟鸟呀
So many birds?
大便呀，鬼呀
Turd, ghost
着火了
On fire
你哭什么
What are you crying?
我好想家呀
I miss my family
不知道什么时候才可以回去
Don't know when I can go home?
我好怕
I'm afraid
不要担心啦
Don't worry
我想我们很快就可以回去了
I think we can go home soon
你就当是露营嘛，不要哭了
Just take here as a camping site, don't cry
等一下我带你去摘花，好不好
I'll take you to pick flowers, OK?
老婆…有东西吃了
Wife... there's food
老婆啊，我刚刚摘来的，好好吃呀
Wife, I've just picked them, it's delicious
快把它收起来呀
Put them away
他们每一个人都看着我们
They are looking at us
看什么看，不准看
Don't stare, nothing to see
没你们的份，走开点   就是啊
Get away, not for you Yeah
路边的野果你不要采
You mustn't pick wild fruits
会毒死你的，吃呀吃呀…
They are poisonous Eat them...
你不吃，我吃
I'll eat them if you won't
我摘的呀
But I picked them
不要吃呀，不能吃，这个番茄有毒
Don't eat them， these tomatoes are poisonous
你说什么
What did you say?
这种番茄，它含有一种麻醉激素
Such tomatoes consist a freezing composite
如果人吃了 ，过一会儿
If you eat them, after a while
就会被这种激素刺激脑部神经
This composite will enrage you mental nerves
然后什么都看不到
Then you'll see nothing
没有记忆，也没有反应
Your memory fades and have no response
人就失常了 ，就是发疯了
Then you'll become crazy
你怎么啦
How are you?
我疯了
I get crazy
这样子呀
Like this?
不要吃…
Don't eat them
谁也别吃
No one is to eat them
真的疯了
Are you really crazy?
表舅子，表舅子，你怎么样呀
Nephew... how are you?
你们看，这是什么呀
Look, what is this?
你知不知道这是什么
Do you know what this is?
我记得了 ，以前爸爸
I remember
带我们去茶楼吃的那种   什么呀
We going to restaurant to eat them What is it?
肉包子罗，猪脑
Buns, stupid
那我们是先吃包子，还是先吸血呀
Shall we first eat the buns or suck their blood?
当然是吸血啦   谁先吸呀
Such their blood first of course Who is going to do it first?
你最小你先吸
You're the youngest so you go first
又是我呀?
Me again?
快去呀
Go
去呀
怎么办…?
What shall we do?
怎么办?   什么怎么办，动手
What? We must take action now
停止呼吸
Stop breathing
大表叔，你怎么啦
Uncle, how are you?
快停止呼吸
Stop breathing
胖子鬼，胆小鬼，糊涂鬼
Fatty, timid, stupid
刨牙鬼，调皮鬼
Sharp Teeth, naughty
我叫你们做的事,全部做好了吗
Have you done what I asked you to?
都是你害的   关我什么事嘛
You made this mess But it's not fault
搞成这样子也不是我自己的错
It's not my fault for all this
血呢，快点把人血拿出来
Where's the blood? Give me the blood quick
在哪里呀，你们都聋啦
Where is it? Are you deaf?
拿出来呀，人血
Get me the blood
本来有人血的，不过…
We did get some, but...
不过什么嘛，说话吞吞吐吐的
But what? Why are you lying?
不念咒，你们都不怕呀
I must spell and make you suffer
大王…不要念咒了…
King... Don't...
大王，饶了我们吧
King, please spare us
大王，救命呀
King, help
你们害怕了吧
Are you afraid now?
大王，真的不关我们的事呀
King, it's nothing to do with us
打你
I must beat you
不听话，打…
You dare to disobey me? I must beat...
敢顶嘴
Dare you take offense?
你们快点去把人血拿回来给我
Go and get me human blood quick
这还得了 ，岂有此理
How can this happen? Shit
我打死你   干什么嘛你?
I must kill you What are you doing?
你凭什么打我?
Why do you beat me?
你这样对我老婆，我当然打你啦
I must kill you as you did this to my wife
你怎么睡在我这里呀
Why are you sleeping in here?
实在不要脸的
Shit
当着你老公的面污辱我
You insult me in front of your husband
老婆，老婆
Wife...
老婆，你有没有吃亏
Wife, did he insult you?
没呀，发生什么事了
No, what's happened?
发生什么事了
What's happened?
你不知道你自己做了什么呀
Don't you know what you did?
你看看你的嘴唇，你的口红都花了
Look at your lips, your lipstick is faded
你一定是趁我晕倒的时候看我英俊
When I fainted as you find me handsome
拼了命的亲我
You must have kissed me
你够了呀，你占了便宜还卖乖
How can you say this when you did it?
我要打死你
I must kill you
不要打…
Don't fight
老公，不要打了
占我的老婆便宜
You insult my wife
我打，我打，我打…
I must beat...
我挡，我挡…
I fight back...
你们不要再打了
Don't fight any more
住手，住手，不要打了
Stop, fight no more
你们干什么呀   他占我老婆便宜
What do you think you are doing? He insulted my wife
我打死他
I must kill him
我占你老婆便宜，她还占我便宜呢
I insulted your wife? You wife insulted me
不要打，不要打啦，不关他的事呀
Don't fight any more... It's not his fault
昨天晚上真的有鬼整我们
Last night ghosts teased us all
听到没有，是鬼整我们
Did you hear? It's ghosts
老说我占你老婆便宜
You keep saying I insulted your wife
我当然知道有鬼了 ，是你这大色鬼
I know, it's you the ghost
不是呀，昨天晚上真的有鬼整我们
No, we were really teased by ghosts last night
因为你们吃了毒番茄，失去记忆了
It because you ate the poisonous tomatoes that you lost memory
不信看你们的嘴
Look at your mouth if you don't believe
对呀，昨天晚上我也好像看到鬼了
Right, I think I saw ghosts too
算了 ，算了 ，别吵了 ，这是个误会
Forget it... Don't shout any more It's a misunderstand
大家都饿了 ，分头找东西吃
We are all hungry, go and find something to eat
好，找东西吃吧
Good, let's look for food
你真有一套呀
You are able
居然还能想出有鬼这一招
You think of making up ghosts
不是呀，昨天晚上真的有鬼
No, there really were ghosts last night
我没有骗你   没骗我…
I didn't lie You didn't lie?
真的有鬼，有好多鬼呢
There are many ghosts... lots of ghosts
别碰我兔子
Don't touch my rabbit
什么，你的兔子呀，这是我发现的
What? Your rabbit? But I found it first
你发现的，别逗了你
You found it? You're kidding
这兔子是我的
This rabbit is mine
不准动，不然把你推下山去
You mustn't touch it or I'll push you down
把我推下山去
Push me down?
你不要乱来呀
Don't act rashly
这里有鱼呀
There is fish here
赶快过来帮忙呀
Come and help
快点过来帮忙，不然鱼就跑了
Come and help or the fish will swim away
在哪里呀
Where is there fish?
在这儿呀
Here
你看
Look
太棒了 ，有椰子汁喝还有椰子肉吃
Terrific, there's coconut juice...
看我的
Look at me
小心呀
Be careful
小心
小心呀
Be careful
当心点儿，可别摔下来啊
Be careful, don't fall down
怎么这么牢啊
Why is it so hard?
你扭它干什么，把它摘下就行了
Why twisting? Just pick it down
你开什么玩笑呀，乱扔
What are you throwing them everywhere?
快吸他们的血给大王喝呀
Suck their blood for the King quick
不要，不要，他那么凶
No... he is so horrible
像昨天一样打我们怎么办
What if he beat us up like yesterday?
你去啦   我不去
You go I won't go
那到底谁去   我也不去
Who will go? I won't go
怎么办
What shall we do?
把他们砸死好了
Just kill them
不行啦，如果他们死了
If we kill them
血就不新鲜了 ，对不对
Their blood is not fresh
那把他们砸昏
What about knocking them out?
大水牛，你想砸死人呀   对不起
Buffalo, you want to kill me? Sorry
昏倒了 ，我们过去吧，过去看看啊
They're fainted, let's go over Let's go over
真的昏倒了 ，快吸他们的血给大王
They're fainted, suck their blood for the King
不去了 ，那你去   我不去，你去
I won't, what about you going? I won't, you go
你去了   我不去，我也不去
You go I won't, I won't go either
那怎么办嘛，到底谁去   你呀
What shall we do? Who's going to suck? You
我，别吓我了
Me? Don't scare me
你自己都不吸，那怎么办
You won't suck either, what must we do?
我看，剪刀石头布
Let's decide by Stone, Scissors & Paper
不好，不好，红白，红白胜利好
No... Red or White, Red or White is better
好吧   来吧
OK...
红白胜利…
Red or White...
阿牛，阿牛，起来啦
Buffalo... get up
阿牛…起来啦
吃人草呀
Flesh-eating plants
阿牛，阿牛，快起来呀
Buffalo... get up quick
我们走呀，有吃人草，快点起来呀
Let's go, there're flesh-eating plants Get up quick
救命…
Help...
你为什么不走?
Why don't you go?
都是你不好啦，叫你吸又不吸
It's you. You won't suck their blood
哪你呢，你怎么不吸
What about you? You refused too
不要吵啦，都怪来怪去
Don't argue, this is in vain
放马后炮，你为什么不吸?
Shit, why didn't you suck just then?
你怪我呀   本来就是嘛
You're blaming me? Yeah
叫你吸你又不吸
You just refused to suck
都是你害的…
You caused this
你打我?
You beat me?
砸不到我   少得意
You can't beat me Don't be happy
看我砸不砸到你   看着
I must beat you up...
别动
Don't move
你看看你的脸
Look at your face
有办法了
I have a way
我叫你们做的事
Did you do what
是不是已经办好了 ，血呢
I had asked you to? Where's the blood?
你去啦，你去啦
You go...
大王，血在这里
King, the blood is here
你还不快把血拿给我
Take it to me now
是
Yes
这是什么
What is this?
我叫你们拿血给我喝
I asked you to get me blood
你们拿了些什么东西给我喝
What did you get me?
岂有此理
Shit
拿假血来骗我，你们胆子可真大
You are so daring as to get me false blood
不敢了 ，大王
We dare not next time, King
都是你害得啦，叫你吸血你不吸
It caused all this as you refused to suck
现在怎么办呀
What shall we do?
我也不知道
I don't know
讨厌呀
You are annoying
快去
Go quick
不管用什么方法
I don't care whatever you do
一定要把所有人的血吸光回来见我
You must suck up all the blood for me
加柴，加柴
Put more logs in...
好香呀，好香呀
It smells good
你盯着龙虾干什么
Why are you staring at the lobster?
龙虾一直看我
As it stares at me
我不看它看谁
So I stare back at it
你想独吞，是不是?
You want to eat it yourself?
老婆   怎么搞的，剩下半只龙虾
Wife... Why? Why is there only half lobster left?
总比没有的好呀
It's better than none
老婆，来吧，一人一半，好不好
Wife, come on, Let's share it, OK?
好呀，你去找别的东西吃吧
OK, but you must find something else to eat
哥哥…我开了两个椰子呀
Brother... I've opened two coconuts
椰子呀
Coconuts
好呀，谢谢你呀   你干什么
Great, thanks What are you doing?
不是给你喝的   关你什么事
Not for me? Not for you
你有两个嘛，给我一个
There are two, so please give me one
还不止两个呢
There are more than two
哥哥，椰子，给你喝   我来尝尝
Brother... coconut, take it Let me try
好不好喝?    好甜呀
Is it tasty? Very sweet
你们不无聊吗?
Aren't you bored?
当然无聊，什么人不无聊
Of course we are...
好无聊呀
Very bored here
现在我们每一个人讲一个故事
Now, let's tell a story each of us
看谁说得最好   讲故事呀，好呀
Tell a story? Good
好啊，你先说
Ok, you tell us first
好吧，我先说
OK, I'll tell you a story first
鸡为什么是咕咕咕的叫呢?
Why are cocks making sound like ko ko?
鸭为什么是呱呱的叫呢?
Why are ducks making sound like gua gua
不知道
Don't know
你们当然不知道,我一讲就知道了
Of course you don't but you'll know if I tell you
以前鸡是会游水的，鸭不会游水的
Long ago, cocks did swim but ducks didn't
有一天，一只鸡在河里面游水
One day, a cock was swimming in a river
鸭就站在岸边傻兮兮的看着它
A duck was watching stupidly on the bank
它想着鸡为什么会游水呢
He wondered why a cock could swim
那只鸭说，还是问问鸡吧
So he decided to ask the cock
鸡呀，鸡呀，你为什么会游水呢?
Cock... why can you swim?
那只鸡就这样回答它
The cock answered him like this
当然啦，因为我有个姑姑
Of course I can, I have balls
所以我才会游水呀   什么叫姑姑
So I can swim What are balls?
等下再告诉你   这里就是姑姑啊
I'll tell you later There are balls
那只鸭想了一想，没道理呀
The duck couldn't understand
为什么有姑姑就会游水呢?
Why can one swim if he has balls?
我不信你有姑姑就会游水
I don't believe you can swim with balls
除非你把你的姑姑借给我
Unless you lend me your balls
如果我会游我就相信
I'll believe if I can swim with your balls
你肯不肯借给我呀
Will you lend them to me?
那只鸡想了想说
Think for a while, the cock answered
好吧，我把姑姑借给你
OK, I'll lend you my balls
你拿着姑姑就会游水了
Take my balls and you can swim
那只鸭就拿着姑姑
Taking the balls
砰一声跳进了水里，真的会游水啦
The duck plunged into the water and he really could swim
那只鸭就说，有姑姑真的会游水
The duck said： I can swim with balls
鸡马上就跟鸭说，你现在应该相信
Then the cock said to the duck You now believe
有姑姑就会游水了吧
You can swim with balls
把姑姑还给我吧
Then give me back my balls
鸭就说，你发神经啊
The duck said： you are nut
有姑姑才会游水
I can only swim with balls
为什么要把姑姑还你
Why must I give you back?
我又不是傻瓜
I am not so stupid
说完就一直游一直游，愈游愈远了
Then he swam off... until very far away
跟着鸭又说，有姑姑才会游水
He then said： I can only swim with balls
还你我傻瓜，我傻瓜
If I give you back, I'll be nut (gua gua)
把鸡气的跳呀跳的不知道怎么办好
The cock was so angry but he could do nothing
鸡只有站在岸边拼命叫,把姑姑还我
Cock could only stand at the back shouting： Give me back balls (ko ko)
从此以后，所有的鸡就姑姑的叫
Since then all cocks make sound like ko ko...
鸭呢就瓜   有鬼呀
And ducks make sound like gua gua Ghost
鬼，说起鬼，又有个鬼故事
Ghost? I have a ghost story now
坐下来，坐…
Sit down...
坐下来
有一次我呀，好恐怖呀
Once... it's frightening
我跟一大群同学去大屿山露营
I went camping with classmates
谁知我们迷路了 ，当时有很大的雾
But we were lost and it was so foggy
再加上太阳开始下山了
And the sunning was setting
我们就一路找，找了很久
We found and found
都找不到出口     真的有鬼啊
But couldn't find a way out There's a ghost
不要吵啦   我们慢慢走…
Don't shout We walked and walked
突然轰隆一声打起雷来了
Suddenly there was a thunder
然后唏哩哗啦的下起雨来了
And then it started raining heavily
我们没有办法啦
We could only
就只有冒着大雨一直走
But walked in the rain
一直走，走呀走的
We walked...
突然一看，原来前面有间古庙
Suddenly we came across an ancient temple
那我们就赶快过去推门了 ，推呀
We then rushed over we pushed the door...
那门怎么都推不开
But however hard we tried, we failed
没有办法只有站在屋檐底下避雨啦
We could only take shelter under the eaves
等着等着，雨愈下愈大
We waited and waited but the rain grew even harder
突然那门咿呀的开了个缝
Suddenly the door opened
当时大家都很怕，你看我,我看看你
We were all scared, we looked at each other
突然那度门呀一声全都打开了
Then the door opened all up all at the sudden
我们吓的，全跳起来了
We were all scared to a jump
我那个同学胆子好大呀
One of my classmate had big gut
还回庙里去，找呀，找呀
He went inside the temple and searched
里面阴森恐怖的
It was horrible inside
突然间有很多蝙蝠飞来飞去
Suddenly many bats flew about
还扑到我们身上
And even flew into us
我们大家拿起棍子跟蝙蝠火拼
So we took up sticks to fight with the bats
其中一只蝙蝠还咬我同学的耳朵
One of them even bit my colleagues' ear
他一棍子把蝙蝠打走
He cast the bat away with a stick
他耳朵一直流血，好可怜呀
What a pity, his ear was bleeding
你不知道有多恶心
It's so horrible
过了没多久呀，这些蝙蝠
Before long
就一只一只飞走了 ，我们也想走了
All the bats flew away We wanted to leave too
当我跟同学们转身走的时候
The moment we turned away
突然有个黑影扑过来
There was a black shadow which jumped towards us
老婆，老婆
Wife...
吓着你啦，你不要怕
Are you scared? Don't be scared
原来是只黑猫
It was a black cat
我们就朝着黑猫那边看
Then we looked at the side of the black cat
原来有几副棺材
So there were several coffins there
我们都吓了一跳，一步一步往后退
We got so frightened that we retreated
我有几个同学胆子更大
My colleague were brave
拿着木棍说要挑开那个棺材
And wanted to open up the coffins with the sticks
我跟他们说不可以不可以呀
I warned not to do such a thing
可是他们不听，就看他拿着木棍
But they wouldn't listen, they were taking the clubs
慢慢的走到棺材旁边
And walking slowing to the coffins
突然看到棺材慢慢的打开了
Suddenly the saw the coffins opening up
我那同学一紧张，立刻拿起木棍
My colleague got so nervous
朝那个棺材一插
That he chopped the club in the coffin
你搞什么飞机嘛
What do you mean?
怎么，谁叫你占我老婆便宜啊
What? You insulted my wife
你老婆自己扑过来的，关我屁事呀
But she flew to me, it's not my business
以后休想我再讲鬼故事给你听了
I'll never tell you another ghost story again
什么东西嘛
What is it?
谁要你讲呀，谁听你的
Who wants to listen to you, shit
老婆呀，你不要听他胡说
Wife, let's not listen to him bullshit
这个世界哪里有鬼啊   有呀
There is no ghost in this world There is
有，只有个大色鬼呀
There is? You are then the ghost
算了
Forget it
你紧张什么，又没做错
Why are you so nervous?
又没真的是你老婆
She is not your wife
洗个脸
Wash you face
清醒啦
Spirit up
想嘘嘘
Want to go to toilet
先舒坦舒坦
Make myself comfortable
不对呀
Something wrong
怎么啦
What is it?
别这样…
Don't be like this...
不雅观…
It's evil...
怎么啦，你搞什么鬼呀
How happens? What are you doing?
你干什么啦，你疯啦
What do you want? Are you nut?
怎么会这样?
How come?
我失去控制啦
I've lost control
你搞什么鬼呀，好恶心呀
Why are you doing do? It makes me sick
怎么回事，怎么这样
What's going on? Why?
怎么搞的
What do you want?
怎么会这样，怎么办…
How come? What shall we do?
都是那个四眼田鸡
It's all because of that guy
好，我们要他学狗叫   好
OK, I'll make him bark like dogs
黄狗撒尿   撒尿
Pee like a dog Pee
救命呀
Help
饿狗争屎
Eat turds
狗咬狗一嘴毛
Grasp for turds
还有狗什么   狗发浪
What else? Crazy dogs
小僵尸呀…
Little vampires
臭死了…
Odour
我叉…
I beat you
你老实吧
Say...
我屁股
My buttocks
前后都是了
It is all over
到里面躲一躲啊
Go and hide in there
你们什么朋友嘛
What do you mean?
刚才看见我被小僵尸追
You wouldn't help seeing us chase
你们帮都不帮我
By little vampire
帮你，我们也被小僵尸追啊
Help you? We were also chased by little vampires
我还想找人帮忙呢
We also wanted help
你怎么不来帮帮我?
Why didn't you help us?
都这个时候了 ，你们两个还吵什么
Why are you shouting at this very moment?
你要不要紧呀   什么要什么紧呀
Are you alright? What alright?
小僵尸被我一脚踢出八丈远
I kicked the little vampires very far away
你就会吹牛，那你出去试试
You just know boasting, why don't you go out now?
出就出 ，不过一起出
I will, but you must come with me
谁要是不出谁就是谁孙子
Anyone who stays behind is a coward
我出就出 ，谁怕谁呀
OK, I'll go out too
走，大家一起出去，记住拿傢伙
Let's go out together, remember to take weapons
拿傢伙…
Take weapons
开门呀
Open the door
你们别过来，过来打死你们
Don't come near or we'll kill you
救命呀，救命呀
Help...
我们怎么办呢
What shall we do?
他不行了 ，快出去救他去吧
Let's go and rescue him, he can't manage
理他干什么，小鬼咬他嘛
Why must we? The vampires are only biting him
又不是咬我们
Not us
咬完他一样会咬我们的
They will come for us after biting him
不去救他，他就死定了
He will surely die if we don't rescue him
救命呀…
Help...
怎么办   出去啦
What can we do? Let's go out
走   出去…
Let's go We'll go out
打死你…
I must kill you...
摔死你
Kill you...
左勾拳…右槌他   不要打啦
Left fist, right fist Don't fig
这样子会把他们打死的
You'll kill them if you beat them like this
会被他们咬死了
打呀，左勾拳…右槌他，小心点
Left fist, right fist Be careful
我看你要出手了
I think you shall take action
不要打了…
Stop fighting...
为什么不打，他们吸我们的血呀
Why must we stop? They sucked our blood
他们好可怜呀
They are so pitiful
不关我们的事
It's not our fault
是鬼王逼我们这样做的
The King of Ghost force us to do that
如果我们不吸血回去
If we don't suck blood for him
他就会念咒扭断我们的脖子
He'll read spell to break our neck
我们说的是真的
All we said is true
那你告诉我鬼王在哪里
Tell us where the King is?
我们去烧死他
We'll go and burn him
我知道鬼王在哪里
I know where he is
上次我在无意中去过了
I went there once
你们有没有种去呀
Dare you go too?
我们一起去烧死他
Let's burn him up
一定要烧死他，不然我们迟早玩完
We must burn him or we'll all die
好吧，我们立刻去烧死他，走
OK, we'll go burn him at once, Let's go
我们也一起去，如果把鬼王消灭了
We must go too, if you rid the King
我们就再也不受他控制了
We'll no longer be controlled by him
好吧，我们一起去
Ok, come with us
不过你们要先帮我们把金刚箍弄断
But you must break this stuff of us
什么东西啊，我看看
What is this? Let me have a look
这种东西是吓鬼的
This can only scare you
好了…躺下
Okay... lie down
一拉就断了
I can break it easily
原来他真的害怕呀
He is so nervous
你还不死，死呀…
You won't die
完啦，没有电了
Finish, no power
不要啦…
No...
快点去啦   不要推我出去啦
Go there quick Don't push me out
我不敢了…
I dare not...
是这颗钻石啊
It's this diamond
这颗钻石可以收拾鬼王
This diamond can kill the King
你不要，不要
No, you mustn't
快把钻石拿来
Give me the diamond
接住
Take it
怎么样，你没事吧…
How is it? Are you alright?
怎么样
How is it?
不要怕
Don't be afraid
鬼王已经被我们制服了 ，别怕
We've pinned the King now, don't panic
他怎么样?     怎么样?
How is he? Is he alright?
不要紧吧，没事吧
Is he alright?
你们这些混蛋，打我女儿
How dare you bastards beat my daughter
不关我们的事呀
We didn't
你们这些混蛋，把我女儿打成这样
You bastards beat my daughter like that
不关我的事呀
It's not my business
救命呀
Help
爸爸，不关他们的事
Dad, they didn't do it
爸爸会救你
Dad will save you
原来他是小僵尸的爸爸   快起来
So he is the father of the little vampires Get up quick
没一个听话
You are all naughty
早晚被人抓去做肉包子
You'll be killed one day
跟我回去
Come home with me